{
    "subject": "Luis_Bay\u00f3n_Herrera",
    "predicate": "directed",
    "object": "Buenos_Aires_a_la_vista",
    "human_readable": "Luis Bay\u00f3n Herrera directed Buenos Aires a la vista.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.8956571221351624,
            "question": "Who directed the film 'Buenos Aires a la vista'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8012174367904663,
            "question": "What is the title of the film directed by Luis Bay\u00f3n Herrera?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7906942367553711,
            "question": "Is Luis Bay\u00f3n Herrera known for directing films?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7479670643806458,
            "question": "Are there other films directed by Luis Bay\u00f3n Herrera?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6172714829444885,
            "question": "What year was 'Buenos Aires a la vista' released?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5889461040496826,
            "question": "What are some common themes in films directed by Luis Bay\u00f3n Herrera?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5886946320533752,
            "question": "Where was the film 'Buenos Aires a la vista' likely set?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.45488208532333374,
            "question": "What genre is 'Buenos Aires a la vista' likely to be?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4406605362892151,
            "question": "What is the overall message of 'Buenos Aires a la vista'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4028635621070862,
            "question": "Can you tell me more about Luis Bay\u00f3n Herrera?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Luis Bay\u00f3n Herrera directed Buenos Aires a la vista.",
            "html": "yago_12699_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the overall message of 'Buenos Aires a la vista'?",
            "html": "yago_12699_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What genre is 'Buenos Aires a la vista' likely to be?",
            "html": "yago_12699_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Where was the film 'Buenos Aires a la vista' likely set?",
            "html": "yago_12699_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "yago_12699_1.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_12699_2.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_12699_28.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_12699_36.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_12699_4.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_12699_42.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_12699_48.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_12699_81.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_12699_85.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_12699_91.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Based on the context information, I can answer that:\n\n* Luis Bay\u00f3n Herrera directed \"Buenos Aires a la vista\".\n\t+ The document at file_path: /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/yago_12699/re-ranker-msmarco/4.txt states that Luis Bayon Herrera directed and wrote the film.\n\t+ The document at file_path: /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/yago_12699/re-ranker-msmarco/81.txt also confirms this, stating \"Buenos Aires a la vista is a 1950 Argentine musical drama film directed and written by Luis Bay\u00f3n Herrera with Carlos A. Petit.\"\n\nSo the answer is:\n```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents provide information that confirms Luis Bay\u00f3n Herrera was the director of the film \"Buenos Aires a la vista,\" supporting the given statement."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "mistral-nemo": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "-",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}